<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/collections/streaming-platforms.atom"/>
  <title>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD</title>
  <updated>2024-06-30T22:49:58+06:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8529583472789</id>
    <published>2024-06-30T22:49:58+06:00</published>
    <updated>2024-06-30T22:49:58+06:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/ullu-subscription-bangladesh"/>
    <title>Ullu Premium Subscription</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0641/0738/0885/files/ullu-price_in_bangldesh.jpg?v=1729881501"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            449.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><strong>Buy Ullu Premium Subscription in Bangladesh – Exclusive Content at Your Fingertips via FanFlixBD</strong></p>
<p><strong>Ullu</strong> is a popular streaming platform known for its bold and original content, including web series, movies, and shows across various genres. With an <strong>Ullu Premium</strong> subscription, you gain access to a vast library of exclusive content, ensuring you never run out of entertainment.</p>
<h3>Why Choose Ullu Premium?</h3>
<p>An Ullu Premium subscription provides numerous benefits for avid viewers:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Exclusive Originals</strong>: Enjoy a wide range of Ullu Originals, including thrilling series and captivating movies not available anywhere else.</li>
<li>
<strong>Ad-Free Experience</strong>: Stream your favorite shows and movies without any interruptions from advertisements.</li>
<li>
<strong>High-Quality Streaming</strong>: Experience your content in high definition, ensuring a visually stunning viewing experience.</li>
<li>
<strong>Offline Downloads</strong>: Download your favorite shows and movies to watch offline, perfect for on-the-go entertainment.</li>
<li>
<strong>Multiple Genres</strong>: Explore a diverse selection of content, including drama, romance, horror, and more, catering to all tastes.</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Buy Ullu Premium from FanFlixBD?</h3>
<p>Purchasing an Ullu Premium subscription from <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> is quick and easy:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<strong>Select Ullu Premium Plan</strong>: Choose the Ullu Premium subscription option on the FanFlixBD website.</li>
<li>
<strong>Local Payment Methods</strong>: Complete your payment using Bkash, Nagad, or Rocket, making it hassle-free for users in Bangladesh.</li>
<li>
<strong>Instant Activation</strong>: Your Ullu Premium subscription will be activated immediately after payment confirmation and sent to your personal email.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Why Buy Ullu Premium from FanFlixBD?</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Affordable Pricing</strong>: FanFlixBD offers competitive prices for Ullu Premium subscriptions, giving you great value for your entertainment.</li>
<li>
<strong>Secure Local Payments</strong>: Enjoy easy payments without the need for international credit cards or complicated payment processes.</li>
<li>
<strong>Instant Delivery</strong>: Receive your Ullu activation details promptly after payment, so you can start streaming without delay.</li>
<li>
<strong>Customer Support</strong>: Our dedicated support team is ready to assist you with any questions or issues regarding your subscription.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Features of Ullu Premium Subscription:</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Unlimited Streaming</strong>: Access all content without any restrictions on views.</li>
<li>
<strong>Personalized Recommendations</strong>: Get tailored content suggestions based on your viewing preferences.</li>
<li>
<strong>User-Friendly Interface</strong>: Navigate easily through the app to find your favorite shows and movies.</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Activate Ullu Premium?</h3>
<ol>
<li>Download the Ullu app from your device's app store.</li>
<li>Log in to your account using the credentials provided after purchase.</li>
<li>Start exploring the extensive library of Ullu content!</li>
</ol>
<h3>Get Ullu Premium Subscription Today!</h3>
<p>Dive into the world of exclusive entertainment with <strong>Ullu Premium</strong>. Purchase your subscription from <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> today and enjoy unlimited access to captivating content!</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Tags</strong>: Ullu Premium, Buy Ullu, Ullu Subscription Bangladesh, Streaming Service, FanFlixBD Ullu, Exclusive Content, Offline Downloads, Affordable Entertainment</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8529583472789</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">449.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8439039000725</id>
    <published>2024-05-14T00:41:40+06:00</published>
    <updated>2024-05-14T00:41:40+06:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/crunchyroll-premium-subscription-bangladesh"/>
    <title>Crunchyroll Subscription in Bangladesh</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0641/0738/0885/files/Crunchyroll-subscription_in-bangladesh.jpg?v=1731514522"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            499.00 - 899.00
            <a href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/crunchyroll-premium-subscription-bangladesh">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><h2>Crunchyroll Shared Subscription in Bangladesh – Unlimited Anime on FanFlixBD</h2>
<p>Experience the best anime streaming service with Crunchyroll, now available in Bangladesh through <strong>FanFlixBD</strong>. With a <strong>Crunchyroll Subscription in Bangladesh</strong>, you can enjoy access to an extensive collection of anime, Asian dramas, and manga. Stream your favorite anime shows without interruptions, in HD, and with the latest simulcasts from Japan.</p>
<h3>Why Choose Crunchyroll Premium in BD?</h3>
<p><strong>1. Unlimited Access</strong>: Stream over 1,000 anime titles, including top shows like Naruto, One Piece, Attack on Titan, and Demon Slayer.</p>
<p><strong>2. No Ads</strong>: Enjoy seamless, ad-free streaming for an uninterrupted viewing experience.</p>
<p><strong>3. Simulcast from Japan</strong>: Watch the latest anime episodes just one hour after they air in Japan.</p>
<p><strong>4. HD and Full HD Streaming</strong>: Get the best visual experience with HD quality.</p>
<p><strong>5. Exclusive Content</strong>: Access Crunchyroll Originals, Asian dramas, and manga, only available to Premium users.</p>
<h3>Crunchyroll Premium Subscription Pricing at FanFlixBD</h3>
<p>At FanFlixBD, we offer the <strong>Crunchyroll Premium subscription</strong> at unbeatable prices for Bangladesh:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>6 Months Shared Subscription</strong>: 499<strong>৳</strong>
</li>
<li>
<strong>1 Year Shared Subscription</strong>: 899<strong>৳</strong>
</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Buy Crunchyroll Subscription in BD?</h3>
<p>Subscribing to Crunchyroll Premium in BD through FanFlixBD is simple and secure. Here's how you can get started:</p>
<p><strong>⇒</strong>Purchase the <strong>6-month</strong> or <strong>1-year </strong>Crunchyroll Premium Subscription from FanFlixBD.</p>
<p><strong>⇒</strong>Pay securely via <strong>Bkash</strong>, <strong>Nagad</strong>, or <strong>Rocket</strong> for fast, hassle-free transactions.</p>
<h3>Why Choose FanFlixBD for Crunchyroll Premium?</h3>
<p><strong>-Affordable Pricing</strong>: Enjoy Crunchyroll Premium at the best rates in Bangladesh.</p>
<p><strong>-Instant Activation</strong>: Get access to premium features on your Crunchyroll account right after payment.</p>
<p><strong>-Secure Payment Options</strong>: Pay via Bkash, Nagad, or Rocket for a smooth and secure purchase process.</p>
<p>Enjoy your favorite anime series without delays or ads. Subscribe to Crunchyroll Premium through FanFlixBD and dive into the world of anime today!</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Tags</strong>: Crunchyroll Subscription Bangladesh, Crunchyroll Premium BD, Crunchyroll Price Bangladesh, Buy Crunchyroll with Bkash, Crunchyroll Premium Price BD, Watch Anime Bangladesh, Crunchyroll Simulcast BD, Crunchyroll Subscription FanFlixBD</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Crunchyroll</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8439039000725</id>
      <title>6 Month -Shared</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">499.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8439039000725</id>
      <title>12 Month - Shared</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">899.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8336765583509</id>
    <published>2024-04-18T21:07:28+06:00</published>
    <updated>2024-04-18T21:07:28+06:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/zee5-subscriptions"/>
    <title>Zee5 Subscription</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0641/0738/0885/files/zee5-Price_in_bd.jpg?v=1729881710"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            900.00 - 1799.00
            <a href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/zee5-subscriptions">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><strong>Buy Zee5 Subscription in Bangladesh – Access Your Favorite Shows with a VPN via FanFlixBD</strong></p>
<p><strong>Zee5</strong> is a popular streaming service offering a vast library of movies, TV shows, web series, and exclusive content across various genres. With a Zee5 subscription from <strong>FanFlixBD</strong>, you can enjoy premium entertainment from the comfort of your home. Please note that a VPN is required for users in Bangladesh to access Zee5’s content.</p>
<h3>Why Choose Zee5?</h3>
<p>Zee5 provides numerous benefits for streaming enthusiasts:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Diverse Content Library</strong>: Access a wide variety of content, including Bollywood films, regional shows, and original series.</li>
<li>
<strong>Multiple Languages</strong>: Enjoy shows and movies in multiple languages, catering to diverse audience preferences.</li>
<li>
<strong>Ad-Free Experience</strong>: Stream your favorite content without interruptions from advertisements.</li>
<li>
<strong>Offline Downloads</strong>: Download content to watch offline, making it perfect for travel or areas with limited internet access.</li>
<li>
<strong>Exclusive Originals</strong>: Get access to Zee5 Originals, featuring unique stories and engaging characters.</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Buy Zee5 Subscription from FanFlixBD?</h3>
<p>Purchasing a Zee5 subscription from <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> is straightforward:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<strong>Select Zee5 Subscription Plan</strong>: Choose the Zee5 subscription option on the FanFlixBD website.</li>
<li>
<strong>Local Payment Methods</strong>: Pay using Bkash, Nagad, or Rocket for a hassle-free experience in Bangladesh.</li>
<li>
<strong>Instant Activation</strong>: Your Zee5 subscription will be activated immediately after payment confirmation.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Using a VPN for Zee5</h3>
<p>Since Zee5 is geo-restricted, a VPN is required for users in Bangladesh to access its content. Here’s how to set it up:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<strong>Choose a Reliable VPN</strong>: Select a reputable VPN service like NordVPN or Surfshark.</li>
<li>
<strong>Install the VPN</strong>: Download and install the VPN application on your device.</li>
<li>
<strong>Connect to a Server</strong>: Connect to a server located in India to access Zee5.</li>
<li>
<strong>Log in to Zee5</strong>: Visit the Zee5 website or app and log in to start streaming.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Why Buy Zee5 from FanFlixBD?</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Affordable Pricing</strong>: FanFlixBD offers competitive prices for Zee5 subscriptions, providing excellent value.</li>
<li>
<strong>Secure Transactions</strong>: Enjoy a safe shopping experience with local payment options.</li>
<li>
<strong>Customer Support</strong>: Our support team is available to assist you with any questions or issues regarding your subscription.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Get Your Zee5 Subscription Today!</h3>
<p>Dive into a world of entertainment with <strong>Zee5</strong>. Purchase your subscription from <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> today and start enjoying a vast library of content!</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Tags</strong>: Zee5 Subscription, Buy Zee5, Zee5 Bangladesh, Zee5 with VPN, FanFlixBD Zee5, Streaming Service, Offline Downloads, Exclusive Content</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8336765583509</id>
      <title>6 Months + VPN</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">900.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8336765583509</id>
      <title>12 Months + VPN (Personal Mail)</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">1799.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8288409911445</id>
    <published>2024-04-07T21:11:32+06:00</published>
    <updated>2024-04-07T21:11:32+06:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/sonyliv-yearly"/>
    <title>SonyLiv Subscription</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0641/0738/0885/files/sonyliv-subscription_price_in_bd.jpg?v=1729881183"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            990.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><strong>Buy SonyLIV Premium Subscription in Bangladesh – Enjoy Unlimited Streaming via FanFlixBD</strong></p>
<p><strong>SonyLIV</strong> is a popular streaming service that offers a vast collection of movies, TV shows, web series, sports, and original content. With a <strong>SonyLIV Premium</strong> subscription, you can unlock exclusive features and access a diverse range of entertainment options right from the comfort of your home.</p>
<h3>Why Choose SonyLIV Premium?</h3>
<p>A SonyLIV Premium subscription provides users with numerous advantages, making it a go-to platform for streaming enthusiasts:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Extensive Content Library</strong>: Enjoy a wide variety of content, including Bollywood movies, regional shows, and international series.</li>
<li>
<strong>Live Sports Streaming</strong>: Catch live sports events, including cricket, football, and more, ensuring you never miss a match.</li>
<li>
<strong>Ad-Free Experience</strong>: Enjoy your favorite shows and movies without interruptions from ads, enhancing your viewing experience.</li>
<li>
<strong>Exclusive Originals</strong>: Access a collection of exclusive web series and original content produced by SonyLIV, only available to premium subscribers.</li>
<li>
<strong>Multi-Device Support</strong>: Stream on multiple devices, including smartphones, tablets, smart TVs, and computers, for flexibility in viewing.</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Buy SonyLIV Premium from FanFlixBD?</h3>
<p>Purchasing a SonyLIV Premium subscription from <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> is easy and convenient:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<strong>Select SonyLIV Premium Plan</strong>: Choose the SonyLIV Premium subscription option on the FanFlixBD website.</li>
<li>
<strong>Local Payment Methods</strong>: Pay using Bkash, Nagad, or Rocket, making it hassle-free for users in Bangladesh.</li>
<li>
<strong>Instant Activation</strong>: Your SonyLIV Premium subscription will be activated immediately after payment confirmation.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Why Buy SonyLIV Premium from FanFlixBD?</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Affordable Pricing</strong>: FanFlixBD offers competitive prices for SonyLIV Premium subscriptions, ensuring great value for your money.</li>
<li>
<strong>Secure Local Payments</strong>: Use local payment options without needing international credit cards or complicated payment processes.</li>
<li>
<strong>Instant Delivery</strong>: Receive your SonyLIV activation details promptly after payment, allowing you to start streaming without delay.</li>
<li>
<strong>Customer Support</strong>: Our support team is available to assist you with any questions or issues regarding your subscription.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Features of SonyLIV Premium Subscription:</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Unlimited Streaming</strong>: Enjoy unlimited access to a vast library of movies, shows, and live sports events.</li>
<li>
<strong>Offline Viewing</strong>: Download your favorite content to watch offline, perfect for travel or when you have limited internet access.</li>
<li>
<strong>Personalized Recommendations</strong>: Get personalized content suggestions based on your viewing habits for a tailored experience.</li>
<li>
<strong>High-Quality Streaming</strong>: Stream in high definition for an immersive viewing experience.</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Activate SonyLIV Premium?</h3>
<ol>
<li>Download the SonyLIV app or visit the official website.</li>
<li>Log in to your account or create a new one.</li>
<li>Enter the activation code provided by FanFlixBD after purchase.</li>
<li>Start enjoying your favorite shows and movies!</li>
</ol>
<h3>Get SonyLIV Premium Subscription Today!</h3>
<p>Unlock a world of entertainment with <strong>SonyLIV Premium</strong>. Purchase your subscription from <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> today and experience the joy of unlimited streaming!</p>
<p><strong>Tags</strong>: SonyLIV Premium, Buy SonyLIV, SonyLIV Bangladesh, Streaming Service, FanFlixBD SonyLIV, Live Sports Streaming, Exclusive Originals, Affordable Streaming Subscription</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8288409911445</id>
      <title>12 Months</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">990.00</s:price>
      <s:sku/>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8220900360341</id>
    <published>2024-03-15T10:52:56+06:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-15T10:52:56+06:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/iqiyi-subscriptions-price-bangladesh"/>
    <title>IQIYI VIP Subscription</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0641/0738/0885/files/iqiyi-price_in_bd.jpg?v=1729880393"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            349.00 - 1600.00
            <a href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/iqiyi-subscriptions-price-bangladesh">(3 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><strong>iQIYI Subscription in Bangladesh – Enjoy Premium Content via FanFlixBD</strong></p>
<p><strong>iQIYI</strong> is a leading online streaming platform known for its vast collection of Asian dramas, movies, anime, and variety shows. With an iQIYI subscription, you can access high-quality content from China, Korea, Japan, and more. <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> makes it easy for users in Bangladesh to subscribe to iQIYI, allowing you to enjoy your favorite shows and movies with just a few clicks.</p>
<h3>Why Choose iQIYI Subscription?</h3>
<p>With an iQIYI subscription, you gain access to a world of entertainment that caters to diverse tastes. Here are some reasons to subscribe:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Vast Content Library</strong>: Enjoy thousands of titles, including popular dramas, movies, and exclusive content that you won’t find anywhere else.</li>
<li>
<strong>High-Quality Streaming</strong>: Experience content in HD quality, with seamless streaming on multiple devices.</li>
<li>
<strong>Simulcasts and Latest Releases</strong>: Watch the latest episodes of your favorite shows soon after they air, keeping you up-to-date with trending series.</li>
<li>
<strong>User-Friendly Interface</strong>: iQIYI offers an intuitive interface, making it easy to search for and discover new content.</li>
<li>
<strong>Offline Viewing</strong>: Download your favorite shows and movies to watch offline, perfect for traveling or when you have limited internet access.</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Buy iQIYI Subscription from FanFlixBD?</h3>
<p>Purchasing your iQIYI subscription through <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> is straightforward:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<strong>Choose Your Subscription Plan</strong>: Select the iQIYI subscription plan that suits you best (monthly or annual).</li>
<li>
<strong>Secure Payment Options</strong>: Make your payment easily using <strong>Bkash</strong>, <strong>Nagad</strong>, or <strong>Rocket</strong>, ensuring a hassle-free transaction.</li>
<li>
<strong>Instant Activation</strong>: Once your payment is confirmed, your iQIYI subscription will be activated immediately, allowing you to start watching right away.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Why Buy iQIYI from FanFlixBD?</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Affordable Pricing</strong>: Enjoy competitive prices on iQIYI subscriptions tailored for Bangladeshi users.</li>
<li>
<strong>Local Payment Methods</strong>: Skip the hassle of international payment options by using local payment methods like <strong>Bkash</strong>, <strong>Nagad</strong>, or <strong>Rocket</strong>.</li>
<li>
<strong>Quick Delivery</strong>: Receive your subscription details promptly after payment, so you can start streaming without delays.</li>
<li>
<strong>Dedicated Customer Support</strong>: Our support team is available to assist you with any questions or issues related to your iQIYI subscription.</li>
</ul>
<h3>What to Watch on iQIYI?</h3>
<p>iQIYI offers a diverse range of content, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Popular Dramas</strong>: Enjoy hit series from China, Korea, and other Asian countries, including romance, fantasy, and action genres.</li>
<li>
<strong>Variety Shows</strong>: Watch entertaining variety shows featuring your favorite stars and engaging content.</li>
<li>
<strong>Anime</strong>: Access a wide selection of anime titles, perfect for fans of the genre.</li>
<li>
<strong>Movies</strong>: Discover both blockbuster hits and indie films from Asia.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Start Your iQIYI Adventure Today!</h3>
<p>With an <strong>iQIYI subscription</strong>, you have access to endless entertainment options at your fingertips. Join the millions of users enjoying high-quality content from Asia. Purchase your subscription through <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> today and dive into a world of captivating dramas, movies, and more!</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Tags</strong>: iQIYI Subscription Bangladesh, Buy iQIYI Subscription, iQIYI Price Bangladesh, Stream Asian Dramas, iQIYI Online Streaming, FanFlixBD iQIYI, Bkash iQIYI Payment</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8220900360341</id>
      <title>1 Months</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">349.00</s:price>
      <s:sku/>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8220900360341</id>
      <title>3 Months</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">899.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8220900360341</id>
      <title>6 Months</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">1600.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8213216297109</id>
    <published>2024-03-12T16:41:59+06:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-12T16:41:59+06:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/hulu-subscription-price-bangladesh"/>
    <title>Hulu Subscription [VPN REQUIRED]</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0641/0738/0885/files/hulu-subscription_bd.jpg?v=1729879546"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            299.00 - 799.00
            <a href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/hulu-subscription-price-bangladesh">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><strong>Hulu Subscription in Bangladesh – Watch Premium TV Shows &amp; Movies via FanFlixBD</strong></p>
<p><strong>Hulu</strong> is one of the leading streaming platforms in the United States, offering a huge collection of TV shows, movies, and exclusive content. While <strong>Hulu</strong> is not available directly in Bangladesh due to geo-restrictions, with <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> and a VPN, you can access Hulu and enjoy its vast entertainment library.</p>
<h3>Why Subscribe to Hulu?</h3>
<p><strong>Hulu</strong> is known for its combination of current TV shows, exclusive Hulu Originals, and a wide selection of movies. Here’s what makes Hulu a must-have streaming service:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Next-Day Streaming of TV Shows</strong>: Hulu allows you to stream popular TV shows like <em>The Handmaid’s Tale</em>, <em>Brooklyn Nine-Nine</em>, <em>Grey's Anatomy</em>, and more the day after they air in the U.S.</li>
<li>
<strong>Hulu Originals</strong>: Hulu offers an impressive lineup of original series, documentaries, and movies, including <em>Only Murders in the Building</em>, <em>The Bear</em>, <em>Dopesick</em>, and <em>Castle Rock</em>.</li>
<li>
<strong>Diverse Content Library</strong>: From blockbuster movies to indie films, Hulu has a vast library of content across all genres, including action, drama, comedy, and documentaries.</li>
<li>
<strong>Live TV Option</strong>: With Hulu + Live TV (available separately), you can stream live channels, including sports, news, and entertainment, making it a comprehensive streaming service for cord-cutters.</li>
<li>
<strong>Personalized Experience</strong>: Hulu offers personalized content recommendations based on your viewing habits, giving you a tailored entertainment experience.</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Access Hulu in Bangladesh?</h3>
<p>Hulu is restricted to viewers in the U.S., but you can bypass these geo-restrictions with a <strong>VPN (Virtual Private Network)</strong>. Here’s how to access Hulu in Bangladesh:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<strong>Install a VPN</strong>: Choose a reliable VPN provider like <strong>ExpressVPN</strong>, <strong>NordVPN</strong>, or <strong>Surfshark</strong> to connect to a U.S. server.</li>
<li>
<strong>Connect to a U.S. Server</strong>: Once the VPN is installed, select a U.S. server to appear as if you're browsing from within the United States.</li>
<li>
<strong>Subscribe to Hulu</strong>: Visit the Hulu website and subscribe using a valid payment method. You can also buy a <strong>Hulu subscription</strong> through <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> for easier payment options.</li>
<li>
<strong>Start Streaming</strong>: After setting up your account and VPN, you can stream Hulu’s vast collection of shows and movies from Bangladesh.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Hulu Subscription Plans from FanFlixBD</h3>
<p>At <strong>FanFlixBD</strong>, we offer <strong>affordable Hulu subscription plans</strong> so you can enjoy the best of Hulu content without hassle:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Monthly Subscription</strong>: Ideal for users who want to test the waters with a short-term subscription.</li>
<li>
<strong>6-Month Plan</strong>: A great option for those who want to save while enjoying continuous access to Hulu.</li>
<li>
<strong>Annual Subscription</strong>: The most cost-effective plan, giving you a full year of uninterrupted access to Hulu's premium content.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Why Buy Hulu from FanFlixBD?</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Affordable Pricing</strong>: We offer Hulu subscriptions at competitive rates for users in Bangladesh.</li>
<li>
<strong>Secure Payments</strong>: Pay securely through <strong>Bkash</strong>, <strong>Nagad</strong>, or <strong>Rocket</strong> without the need for international credit cards.</li>
<li>
<strong>Fast Delivery</strong>: Once your payment is processed, your Hulu subscription will be activated promptly, allowing you to start streaming immediately.</li>
<li>
<strong>Reliable Customer Support</strong>: If you need help with VPN setup or accessing your Hulu account, our dedicated customer support team is here to assist.</li>
</ul>
<h3>VPN Requirement for Hulu</h3>
<p>Since Hulu is only available in the U.S., you’ll need a <strong>VPN</strong> to access the service from Bangladesh. VPNs like <strong>ExpressVPN</strong> or <strong>NordVPN</strong> are recommended for fast streaming speeds and effective geo-blocking bypassing.</p>
<h3>How to Buy Hulu Subscription from FanFlixBD?</h3>
<ol>
<li>Select your preferred Hulu subscription plan (monthly, 6 months, or annual).</li>
<li>Make payment via <strong>Bkash</strong>, <strong>Nagad</strong>, or <strong>Rocket</strong>.</li>
<li>Get your account details and start streaming Hulu using a VPN.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Enjoy Hulu’s Premium Content Today!</h3>
<p>Whether you're a fan of current TV shows, Hulu Originals, or blockbuster movies, <strong>Hulu</strong> offers an unparalleled streaming experience. Subscribe through <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> today and start watching your favorite shows and movies from anywhere in Bangladesh!</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Tags</strong>: Hulu Bangladesh, Hulu Subscription, Hulu VPN, Buy Hulu with Bkash, Hulu Price in Bangladesh, Watch Hulu in Bangladesh, Hulu Originals, FanFlixBD Hulu Subscription, VPN for Hulu Bangladesh</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8213216297109</id>
      <title>1 Months</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">299.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8213216297109</id>
      <title>3Months</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">799.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8213211283605</id>
    <published>2024-03-12T16:38:35+06:00</published>
    <updated>2024-03-12T16:38:35+06:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/hbo-max-subscriptions-price-bangladesh"/>
    <title>HBO MAX Subscription</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0641/0738/0885/files/hbo-subscription_bangladesh.jpg?v=1729879471"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS BD<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            300.00 - 1999.00
            <a href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/hbo-max-subscriptions-price-bangladesh">(4 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><strong>HBO Max Subscription in Bangladesh – Stream Your Favorite Shows via FanFlixBD</strong></p>
<p><strong>HBO Max</strong> is one of the most popular streaming platforms globally, offering a vast library of movies, TV shows, and original content. However, due to geo-restrictions, <strong>HBO Max is not directly available in Bangladesh</strong>. But with <strong>FanFlixBD</strong>, you can still enjoy HBO Max by using a VPN service. Here’s everything you need to know about accessing HBO Max from Bangladesh.</p>
<h3>Why Choose HBO Max?</h3>
<p><strong>HBO Max</strong> offers an unmatched entertainment experience, providing a wide selection of premium content across various genres. Here’s what makes HBO Max worth subscribing to:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Exclusive HBO Originals</strong>: Stream hit series like <em>Game of Thrones</em>, <em>Succession</em>, <em>Euphoria</em>, <em>Westworld</em>, and many more. Get early access to new HBO shows and exclusive content not available elsewhere.</li>
<li>
<strong>Warner Bros. Blockbusters</strong>: Enjoy blockbuster movies straight from Warner Bros., including the latest theatrical releases available on HBO Max shortly after they hit theaters.</li>
<li>
<strong>DC Universe</strong>: For comic book fans, HBO Max offers a rich selection of DC Universe movies and series, such as <em>The Batman</em>, <em>Zack Snyder's Justice League</em>, <em>Titans</em>, and more.</li>
<li>
<strong>Hollywood Hits &amp; International Content</strong>: In addition to Hollywood classics, HBO Max offers a collection of international content, including popular shows and films from across the world.</li>
<li>
<strong>Family-Friendly Content</strong>: From animated series to family movies, HBO Max has a dedicated section for kids and family-friendly entertainment with top picks like <em>Harry Potter</em>, <em>Looney Tunes</em>, and <em>Studio Ghibli</em> films.</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Access HBO Max in Bangladesh?</h3>
<p>Since <strong>HBO Max is geo-restricted</strong>, you’ll need a <strong>VPN (Virtual Private Network)</strong> to access the service from Bangladesh. Here's how you can do it:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<strong>Install a VPN</strong>: Choose a reliable VPN service such as <strong>ExpressVPN</strong>, <strong>NordVPN</strong>, or <strong>Surfshark</strong> to bypass geo-restrictions.</li>
<li>
<strong>Connect to a US Server</strong>: Once installed, connect your VPN to a <strong>US server</strong> to appear as if you're browsing from the United States.</li>
<li>
<strong>Subscribe to HBO Max</strong>: After the VPN connection is established, head to the HBO Max website and subscribe using a valid payment method. You can also purchase HBO Max subscriptions through <strong>FanFlixBD</strong>.</li>
<li>
<strong>Start Streaming</strong>: Enjoy HBO Max’s vast library of content from anywhere in Bangladesh.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Why Buy HBO Max from FanFlixBD?</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Affordable Subscription Plans</strong>: FanFlixBD offers competitive pricing for HBO Max subscriptions in Bangladesh. Choose from <strong>monthly</strong>, <strong>6-month</strong>, or <strong>annual plans</strong>.</li>
<li>
<strong>Easy Payment Options</strong>: Securely pay for your subscription via <strong>Bkash</strong>, <strong>Nagad</strong>, or <strong>Rocket</strong> without the need for international credit cards.</li>
<li>
<strong>Fast Delivery</strong>: Once your payment is confirmed, your HBO Max subscription will be activated quickly, and you’ll receive all necessary instructions for accessing the service.</li>
<li>
<strong>Customer Support</strong>: FanFlixBD offers helpful customer support to ensure you have a smooth experience from purchasing to setting up your subscription.</li>
</ul>
<h3>VPN Requirement for HBO Max</h3>
<p>A VPN is necessary to access HBO Max from Bangladesh, as the service is only available in select regions, including the US. <strong>ExpressVPN</strong> is highly recommended for its speed, security, and ability to bypass geo-restrictions effortlessly. Ensure you have a stable VPN connection before starting your streaming journey with HBO Max.</p>
<h3>How to Buy HBO Max Subscription from FanFlixBD?</h3>
<ol>
<li>Select the HBO Max subscription plan (monthly, 6-month, or yearly).</li>
<li>Complete the payment via <strong>Bkash</strong>, <strong>Nagad</strong>, or <strong>Rocket</strong>.</li>
<li>You’ll receive your account login details and instructions on how to access HBO Max using a VPN.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Enjoy Premium Content with HBO Max Today!</h3>
<p>HBO Max brings you premium content with no compromises. Whether you’re into action, comedy, drama, or animated series, HBO Max has something for everyone. Subscribe through <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> today and start enjoying world-class entertainment from the comfort of your home!</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Tags</strong>: HBO Max Bangladesh, HBO Max Subscription, HBO Max VPN, Buy HBO Max with Bkash, HBO Max Price in Bangladesh, Watch HBO Max in Bangladesh, HBO Originals, FanFlixBD HBO Max, VPN for HBO Max Bangladesh</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8213211283605</id>
      <title>1 Month</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">300.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8213211283605</id>
      <title>3 Months</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">799.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8213211283605</id>
      <title>6 Months</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">1299.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8213211283605</id>
      <title>1 Year</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">1999.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8095511740565</id>
    <published>2023-12-09T22:28:07+06:00</published>
    <updated>2023-12-09T22:28:07+06:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/apple-tv-subscriptions-bangladesh"/>
    <title>Apple TV + Subscription</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0641/0738/0885/files/apple-tv_Subscription_in_bangaldesh.jpg?v=1729878694"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            299.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p> </p>
<p><strong>Before purchasing Apple TV, please note the following Terms of Service:</strong></p>
<p><span><span class="Apple-tab-span"> </span></span><span>1.</span><span><span class="Apple-tab-span"> </span></span><span>You must add a valid payment method to your App Store account to redeem the code. If you do not have a payment method or credit card, we provide instructions on how to set up Apple Cash.</span></p>
<p><span><span class="Apple-tab-span"> </span></span><span>2.</span><span><span class="Apple-tab-span"> </span></span><span>After reviewing our instructions, if you still do not understand how to use Apple Cash, we will not provide further support, issue refunds, or be held responsible for any issues that may arise.</span></p>
<p><strong>Important: Only new users who have not previously redeemed this offer are eligible.</strong></p>
<p>If you agree to these terms, feel free to proceed with your purchase.<br><strong></strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Buy Apple TV+ Subscription with Redeem Code – FanFlixBD</strong></p>
<p>Looking to enjoy premium content from <strong>Apple TV+</strong>? Now you can easily purchase a <strong>3-month Apple TV+ subscription</strong> at <strong>FanFlixBD</strong>, redeemable on your personal account for the <strong>USA region</strong>. Whether you're looking for the latest movies, exclusive TV shows, or original Apple content, <strong>Apple TV+</strong> is the ultimate streaming platform.</p>
<h3>How to Redeem Apple TV+ Subscription Code:</h3>
<p>Buying and redeeming your <strong>Apple TV+ subscription</strong> is simple:</p>
<ol>
<li>Purchase the <strong>3-month subscription</strong> from <strong>FanFlixBD</strong>.</li>
<li>Receive your <strong>redeem code</strong> instantly via Whatsapp</li>
<li>Log in to your <strong>Apple account</strong>.</li>
<li>Head to the <strong>Redeem Code</strong> section.</li>
<li>Enter your code, and enjoy <strong>3 months of unlimited streaming</strong>.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Why Choose FanFlixBD for Apple TV+ Subscription?</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Instant Delivery</strong>: Receive your redeem code right after purchase.</li>
<li>
<strong>Convenient Payments</strong>: Pay easily with <strong>Bkash</strong>, <strong>Nagad</strong>, or <strong>Rocket</strong>.</li>
<li>
<strong>Affordable Pricing</strong>: Get 3 months of <strong>Apple TV+</strong> at an unbeatable price.</li>
<li>
<strong>Safe and Secure</strong>: Purchase with confidence and redeem on your personal Apple account for the <strong>USA region</strong>.</li>
</ul>
<p>At <strong>FanFlixBD</strong>, we ensure you get a hassle-free shopping experience for your <strong>Apple TV+ subscription</strong>. Whether you’re a fan of critically acclaimed TV shows, blockbuster movies, or award-winning series, Apple TV+ has everything you need.</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Tags:</strong> Buy Apple TV+ Subscription Bangladesh, Apple TV+ Redeem Code BD, 3-Month Apple TV+ Subscription USA, FanFlixBD Apple TV+, Apple TV+ with Bkash, Apple TV+ Payment Nagad, Apple TV+ Bangladesh</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8095511740565</id>
      <title>1 Month</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">299.00</s:price>
      <s:sku/>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8095492964501</id>
    <published>2023-12-09T21:43:49+06:00</published>
    <updated>2023-12-09T21:43:49+06:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/dinsey-hotstar-orginal-subscription-bangladesh"/>
    <title>Dinsey+ Hotstar [JioHotstar] Orginal Subscription</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0641/0738/0885/files/Hotstar-premium_price_in_bd.jpg?v=1729946207"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>FANFLIX - OTT SUBSCRIPTIONS<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            2200.00 - 3500.00
            <a href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/dinsey-hotstar-orginal-subscription-bangladesh">(2 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><p><strong>Please Read Before Purchase:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li><strong>✅ Login via QR Code Only</strong></li>
<li><strong>💻 Supports PC, Laptop &amp; TV Only</strong></li>
<li><strong>📵 OTP Login for Mobile Phones &amp; iPads is NOT Available</strong></li>
<li><b>🖥️ Any One Device Login</b></li>
</ul>
<p>Make sure you have access to a compatible device before proceeding with your purchase.</p>
<p><strong>Wide content selectionJioHotstar includes everything from both platforms. This includes Hotstar Specials, Disney, HBO, Peacock, Paramount+, Marvel, Pixar, Star Wars and National Geographic.</strong><strong>Content from TV channelsIn addition to movies and TV shows, the OTT platform also includes shows from TV channels such as Star Plus, ColorHD, ABC Studio, Star World, etc.</strong></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>Disney+ Hotstar Indian Account in Bangladesh – Stream Your Favorite Movies and Shows with FanFlixBD</strong></p>
<p>Experience the magic of <strong>Disney+ Hotstar</strong> with an Indian account, now available through <strong>FanFlixBD</strong>. Enjoy a vast library of movies, TV shows, sports, and exclusive content from Disney, Pixar, Marvel, Star Wars, and National Geographic, all in one place.</p>
<h3>Why Choose Disney+ Hotstar?</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Extensive Content Library</strong>: Access a diverse collection of films and series, including the latest Bollywood blockbusters, popular TV shows, and Disney classics.</li>
<li>
<strong>Live Sports</strong>: Enjoy live streaming of sports events, including cricket, football, and more, all in HD quality.</li>
<li>
<strong>Exclusive Originals</strong>: Watch Disney+ Hotstar Originals and exclusive content that you won’t find anywhere else.</li>
<li>
<strong>Multiple Devices</strong>: Stream on multiple devices, including smartphones, tablets, smart TVs, and desktops.</li>
<li>
<strong>User-Friendly Interface</strong>: Enjoy easy navigation and personalized recommendations based on your viewing preferences.</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Buy a Disney+ Hotstar Indian Account in Bangladesh?</h3>
<p>At <strong>FanFlixBD</strong>, getting your <strong>Disney+ Hotstar Indian account</strong> is simple and secure. Here’s how you can subscribe:</p>
<ol>
<li>Purchase your <strong>Disney+ Hotstar Indian account</strong> from <strong>FanFlixBD</strong>.</li>
<li>The account will be activated directly, allowing you to start streaming immediately.</li>
<li>Pay securely via <strong>Bkash</strong>, <strong>Nagad</strong>, or <strong>Rocket</strong> for a hassle-free experience.</li>
</ol>
<h3>Why Buy from FanFlixBD?</h3>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Affordable Pricing</strong>: Get access to Disney+ Hotstar at the best prices in Bangladesh.</li>
<li>
<strong>Instant Activation</strong>: Enjoy immediate access to your Disney+ Hotstar account after payment.</li>
<li>
<strong>Secure Payment Options</strong>: Choose from <strong>Bkash</strong>, <strong>Nagad</strong>, or <strong>Rocket</strong> for safe transactions.</li>
</ul>
<p>Dive into the world of entertainment with <strong>Disney+ Hotstar</strong>. Subscribe now at <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> and enjoy your favorite movies, shows, and live sports all in one place!</p>
<hr>
<p><strong>Tags</strong>: Disney+ Hotstar Indian Account Bangladesh, Disney+ Hotstar Subscription BD, Buy Disney+ Hotstar with Bkash, Disney+ Hotstar Price Bangladesh, Watch Disney Movies BD, Disney+ Hotstar Live Sports, FanFlixBD Disney+ Subscription</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8095492964501</id>
      <title>6 Months+VPN</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">2200.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8095492964501</id>
      <title>12 Months+VPN</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">3500.00</s:price>
      <s:sku/>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8085334687893</id>
    <published>2023-12-02T10:31:31+06:00</published>
    <updated>2023-12-02T10:31:31+06:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/prime-video-subscription-bangladesh"/>
    <title>Amazon Prime Video</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>FANFLIX BD</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0641/0738/0885/files/amazon-prime_video_subscription_bd.jpg?v=1729878264"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>FANFLIX BD<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            199.00 - 1299.00
            <a href="https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/prime-video-subscription-bangladesh">(4 variants)</a>
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><section data-element_type="section" data-id="1b29e5a" class="elementor-section elementor-top-section elementor-element elementor-element-1b29e5a elementor-section-boxed elementor-section-height-default elementor-section-height-default">
<div class="elementor-container elementor-column-gap-default">
<div data-element_type="column" data-id="05c91d4" class="elementor-column elementor-col-100 elementor-top-column elementor-element elementor-element-05c91d4">
<div class="elementor-widget-wrap elementor-element-populated">
<div data-widget_type="text-editor.default" data-element_type="widget" data-id="9960db0" class="elementor-element elementor-element-9960db0 elementor-widget elementor-widget-text-editor">
<div class="elementor-widget-container">
<div class="flex max-w-full flex-col flex-grow">
<div class="min-h-[20px] text-message flex w-full flex-col items-end gap-2 whitespace-normal break-words [.text-message+&amp;]:mt-5" dir="auto" data-message-id="71e4ac87-1149-4814-a638-7ecb78ed48cd" data-message-author-role="assistant">
<div class="flex w-full flex-col gap-1 empty:hidden first:pt-[3px]">
<div class="markdown prose w-full break-words dark:prose-invert light">
<p><strong>Amazon Prime Video Subscription in Bangladesh – Affordable Streaming with FanFlixBD</strong></p>
<p>Are you a fan of binge-watching the latest movies and TV shows? Now, you can enjoy <strong>Amazon Prime Video</strong> right here in Bangladesh, thanks to <strong>FanFlixBD</strong>! As one of the world’s leading OTT platforms, Amazon Prime Video brings an extensive collection of content, from Hollywood blockbusters and Bollywood hits to exclusive Bangladeshi shows.</p>
<p>In this guide, we'll cover everything you need to know about getting an <strong>Amazon Prime Video subscription in Bangladesh</strong>, including pricing, payment methods, features, and more.</p>
<h3>Overview of Amazon Prime Video in Bangladesh</h3>
<p><strong>Amazon Prime Video</strong> offers a vast library of movies, TV shows, and original content. From blockbuster films to regional hits, Amazon Prime has something for everyone. Subscribers in Bangladesh can enjoy a wide range of content, including <strong>Hollywood</strong>, <strong>Bollywood</strong>, and <strong>Bangladeshi</strong> productions. Plus, you can <strong>download movies and shows</strong> to watch offline whenever you want, perfect for those who are on the go!</p>
<h3>Subscription Fee and Pricing in Bangladesh</h3>
<p>FanFlixBD offers <strong>Amazon Prime Video subscriptions</strong> at competitive prices tailored for the Bangladeshi audience:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Monthly Plan</strong>: Only <strong>99 Taka</strong> per month, perfect for short-term users.</li>
<li>
<strong>Annual Plan</strong>: Get a full year's subscription for just <strong>850 Taka</strong>, offering great value for regular streamers.</li>
</ul>
<p>Compared to other OTT platforms available in Bangladesh, <strong>Amazon Prime Video</strong> provides some of the most affordable pricing options, making premium content accessible to everyone.</p>
<h3>Payment Methods Available in Bangladesh</h3>
<p>FanFlixBD makes it easy for you to subscribe to <strong>Amazon Prime Video</strong> with various local payment options. You can pay conveniently using:</p>
<ul>
<li><strong>Bkash</strong></li>
<li><strong>Nagad</strong></li>
<li><strong>Rocket</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>These widely used payment systems ensure that subscribing to <strong>Amazon Prime Video</strong> is seamless and hassle-free, allowing you to start streaming your favorite content immediately.</p>
<h3>Features and Benefits of Amazon Prime Video</h3>
<p>Amazon Prime Video comes packed with features designed to enhance your viewing experience. Some key benefits include:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Huge Content Library</strong>: Access thousands of movies and TV shows from Hollywood, Bollywood, and Bangladesh.</li>
<li>
<strong>Offline Viewing</strong>: Download content for offline viewing and watch anytime, even without an internet connection.</li>
<li>
<strong>Multi-User Profiles</strong>: Create up to 6 individual profiles on a single account, making it ideal for families or shared subscriptions.</li>
<li>
<strong>Personalized Recommendations</strong>: Get custom suggestions based on your viewing habits for a more tailored experience.</li>
<li>
<strong>High-Quality Streaming</strong>: Enjoy HD and 4K streaming with minimal buffering, offering a smooth and immersive experience.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Why Subscribe to Amazon Prime Video through FanFlixBD?</h3>
<p>At <strong>FanFlixBD</strong>, we make it easier than ever to get your <strong>Amazon Prime Video subscription</strong>. Here’s why you should choose us:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Instant Delivery</strong>: Your subscription will be activated quickly, usually within a few hours.</li>
<li>
<strong>Affordable Pricing</strong>: We offer some of the best rates for Amazon Prime Video in Bangladesh, making premium content affordable.</li>
<li>
<strong>Multiple Payment Options</strong>: Conveniently pay with local payment systems like Bkash, Nagad, and Rocket.</li>
<li>
<strong>Customer Support</strong>: Our dedicated support team is available to assist you with any issues or questions you may have regarding your subscription.</li>
</ul>
<h3>How to Get Your Amazon Prime Video Subscription</h3>
<ol>
<li>
<strong>Visit FanFlixBD</strong>: Navigate to our website and select the <strong>Amazon Prime Video subscription</strong> package that suits your needs.</li>
<li>
<strong>Choose Your Payment Method</strong>: Pay via Bkash, Nagad, or Rocket for a quick and seamless transaction.</li>
<li>
<strong>Start Streaming</strong>: Once your subscription is activated, you can instantly start streaming the latest movies and TV shows on <strong>Amazon Prime Video</strong>.</li>
</ol>
<hr>
<p><strong>Enjoy the Best of Amazon Prime Video in Bangladesh with FanFlixBD!</strong></p>
<p>With affordable pricing, flexible payment options, and an extensive library of content, <strong>Amazon Prime Video</strong> is the perfect platform for anyone who loves quality entertainment. Subscribe today through <strong>FanFlixBD</strong> and start streaming your favorite shows and movies in no time!</p>
<hr>
<h3>Keywords:</h3>
<ul>
<li>Amazon Prime Video Subscription in Bangladesh</li>
<li>Amazon Prime Video Price in BD</li>
<li>Amazon Prime Video Monthly Plan BD</li>
<li>Amazon Prime Video Shop Bangladesh</li>
<li>Prime Video Bangladesh Bkash Payment</li>
<li>Watch Amazon Prime Video in Bangladesh</li>
<li>FanFlixBD Amazon Prime Subscription</li>
<li>OTT Streaming Platforms BD</li>
</ul>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="mb-2 flex gap-3 empty:hidden -ml-2"><br></div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</section></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>Crunchyroll</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Netflix</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Youtube</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8085334687893</id>
      <title>1 Month</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">199.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8085334687893</id>
      <title>3 Months</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">499.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8085334687893</id>
      <title>6 Months</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">799.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.fanflixbd.com/products/8085334687893</id>
      <title>12 Months</title>
      <s:price currency="BDT">1299.00</s:price>
      <s:sku></s:sku>
      <s:grams>0</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
